RG 38.16.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Videotapes, 1993-2005
  - "Ultraviolet Live 2005" (9 tapes), 1 Mar 2005
  - "Absintee Father", 16 Feb 2001 (Box 66)
  - "Bobst 30th Anniversary", unknown (Box 66)
  - "Asian Cultural Expressions" Promo, 1 Jan 2002 (Box 66)
  - "Campus Flash: Community Service 9/11 Educare" Documentary" (4 tapes), unknown (Box 66)
  - "Campus Flash: Community Service Interviews", unknown (Box 66)
  - "A/P/A studies" Hmong Man, 18 Feb 2005 (Box 66)
  - "Bobst Interiors", 26 August 1994 (Box 66)
  - "Gallatin: Dedication", 12 Oct 1995 (Box 66)
  - "King Hussein of Jordan at Bobst Library", 6 Oct 1996 (Box 66)
  - "Attica 25 Anniversary Live Feed from Loeb" (2 tapes), 9 Apr 1997 (Box 66)
  - "King Juan Carlos Dedication", 9 Apr 1997 (Box 66)
  - "Ann Linnehan: Teleconference Opening Interview" Documentary, 10 Feb 1997 (Box 66)
  - "NYU Park Clean Up" Documentary, 21 Apr 1998 (Box 66)
- Series II: Commencement and Founder's Day, 1995-2009
  - "163rd NYU Commencement" VHS, 1995 (Box 16, Reel Project 74)
    Barcode: 31142042272891
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1995 (33 tapes) (Box 27)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1996 (20 tapes) (Box 28)
  - "Founder's Day" Betamax SP, 1997 (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272867
  - "Gallatin Commencement" VHS, 1997 (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - "165th NYU Commencement" VHS (2 tapes), 1997 (Box 16, Reel Project 73)
  - "Bagpipes for Commencement" audio tape, 1997 (Box 21, Reel Project 77)
    Barcode: 31142042272941
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1997 (14 tapes) (Box 29)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1997 (9 tapes) (Box 30)
  - "Grad Alley" Betamax SP (2 tapes)/ Master (1 tape), 1998 (Box 13, Reel Project 65)
  - "166th NYU Commencement (JumboTron video)" Master, 1998 (Box 13, Reel Project 66)
  - "Founder's Day" VHS, 1998 (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272875
  - "166th NYU Commencement" VHS (4 tapes), 1998 (Box 16, Reel Project 66)
  - "Stern Undergraduate Precommencement" VHS, 1998 (Box 21, Reel Project 64)
  - "NYU Grad Alley" Master, 1998 (Box 19, Reel Project 65)
    Barcode: 31142042272925
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1998 (23 tapes) (Box 31)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1998 (13 tapes) (Box 32)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1998 (9 tapes) (Box 33)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1998 (8 tapes) (Box 34)
  - "Founder's Day" VHS, 1999 (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - "Founder's Day" Master (2 tapes), 1999 (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
    Barcode: 31142042272883
  - "167th NYU Commencement" Master (1 tape)/ Betamax SP (2 tapes), 1999 (Box 16, Reel Project 71)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1999 (11 tapes) (Box 35)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1999 (9 tapes) (Box 36)
  - Commencement & Founder's Day Videotapes 1999 (11 tapes) (Box 37)
  - "Stern Undergraduate Precommencement" Betamax SP, 2000 (Box 13, Reel Project 64)
  - "168th NYU Commencement" Master (10 tapes), 2000 (Box 13, Reel Project 67)
  - "168th NYU Commencement" VHS (1 tape)/ Betamax SP (2 tapes), 2000 (Box 14, Reel Project 67)
  - "Stern Graduation" VHS, 2000 (Box 14, Reel Project 64)
  - "Founder's Day" Master (2 tapes), 2000 (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - "Gallatin Commencement" Master (2 tapes), 2000 (Box 16, Reel Project 72)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement" Master (2 tapes), 2000 (Box 16, Reel Project 75)
  - "169th NYU Commencement" VHS (3 tapes), 2001 (Box 14, Reel Project 70)
  - "Founder's Day" Master (3 tapes), 2001 (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - "169th NYU Commencement" Master (4 tapes), 2001 (Box 16, Reel Project 70)
  - "169th NYU Commencement" Master (11 tapes), 2001 (Box 17, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272909
  - "169th NYU Commencement" Master (10 tapes), 2001 (Box 18, Reel Project 70)
    Barcode: 31142042272917
  - "Gallatin Commencement" Master (2 tapes), 2001 (Box 19, Reel Project 72)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Class Day Exercises" Master, 2001 (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - "Founder's Day" VHS (2 tapes)/ Master (1 tape), 2002 (Box 13, Reel Project 63)
  - "170th NYU Commencement" VHS (2 tapes), 2002 (Box 13, Reel Project 68)
  - "Founder's Day" VHS (4 tapes), 2002 (Box 14, Reel Project 63)
  - "Founder's Day" Master (3 tapes), 2002 (Box 15, Reel Project 63)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Commencement" Master (4 tapes), 2002 (Box 19, Reel Project 69)
  - "170th NYU Commencement" Master (8 tapes), 2002 (Box 19, Reel Project 68)
  - "170th NYU Commencement" Master (18 tapes), 2002 (Box 20, Reel Project 68)
    Barcode: 31142042272933
  - "171st NYU Commencement" Master (12 tapes)/ VHS (3 tapes), 2003 (Box 21, Reel Project 76)
  - "171st NYU Commencement" Master (18 tapes), 2003 (Box 22, Reel Project 76)
    Barcode: 31142042272958
  - "172nd NYU Commencement" Master (7 tapes), 2004 (Box 23, Reel Project 78)
    Barcode: 31142042272966
  - "50th Anniversary of Brown vs. Board of Education lecture/panel" Master (3 tapes), May 17, 2004 (Box 23, Reel Project 79)
  - "College of Arts & Sciences (CAS) Commencement" Master (3 tapes), May 11, 2004 (Box 23, Reel Project 80)
  - "172nd NYU Commencement" Master (17 tapes), 2004 (Box 24, Reel Project 78)
    Barcode: 31142042272974
  - "173rd NYU Commencement" Master (16 tapes), 2005 (Box 25, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272982
  - "173rd NYU Commencement" Master (6 tapes), 2005 (Box 26, Reel Project 81)
    Barcode: 31142042272990
  - Commencement Videotapes 2006 (22 tapes) (Box 38)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007 (14 tapes) (Box 39)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007 (10 tapes) (Box 40)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007 (11 tapes) (Box 41)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2007 (8 tapes) (Box 42)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008 (12 tapes) (Box 43)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008 (17 tapes) (Box 44)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008 (15 tapes) (Box 45)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2008 (12 tapes) (Box 63)
  - Commencement Videotapes 2009 (24 tapes) (Box 46)
  - "NYU Logo: Torch 1831" Betamax SP, undated (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
    Barcode:31142042272867
  - "NYU Logo: Bobcat" VHS, undated (Box 13, Reel Project 61)
  - "Silver Convocation" VHS (2 tapes), undated (Box 13, Reel Project 62)
  - "School of Continuing & Professional Studies Ceremonies" VHS (2 tapes)/ Master (1 tape), undated (Box 14, Reel Project 69)
  - "NYU Logo: Torch" Master, undated (Box 19, Reel Project 61)
  - "NYU Logo: Tiffany" Master, undated (Box 21, Reel Project 61)
  - "Unlabelled" VHS (2 tapes), undated (Box 26, Reel Project 82)